<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jacobitosuperstar</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/</link><description>Recent content on jacobitosuperstar</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//jacobobedoya.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ABOUT ME</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/about_me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/about_me/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="about-me">&lt;strong>ABOUT ME&lt;/strong>&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A hardworking and determined individual who harbors a deep passion for the
world of software and automation. With a solid foundation in data analysis and
extensive experience in backend development using Python, I am driven by the
boundless potential of technology and its ability to transform industries and
enhance lives. I am always on the lookout for new challenges and opportunities
to leverage my skills in creative and meaningful ways.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>death of a father</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/death_of_a_father/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/death_of_a_father/</guid><description>&lt;p>My mother and I were waiting for clearance from the hospital to go in to visit
him, my father. At the time of our arrival, he was celebrating his funeral
ritual with a former priest friend of his. His personal nurse was outside
standing with us. We invited her to a coffee. None of us said a word about
anything.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We got there because the night before, his best friend Gustavo, had called us
to tell us about his state, and how my father had been sending his goodbyes
through his cellphone to everyone, except him, my mother and me. I bought the
tickets to Bogota, and we parted the next day at 7:00 am to be at the hospital
at 9:00 am. That was the time when the visits start. His personal nurse got a
call from the priest, we all got up and she went to the reception to talk to
the ladies in charge of the clearance permits. I was the one going up next.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Python Parallelism for Point Cloud Processing</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/parallel_pointcloud_processing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/parallel_pointcloud_processing/</guid><description>&lt;p>LAS and its compressed counterpart LAZ are popular file formats for storing
Point Cloud information, typically generated by LiDAR technology. LiDAR, or
Light Detection and Ranging, is a remote sensing technology used to measure
distances and create highly accurate 3D maps of objects and landscapes. The
Point Cloud information stored mainly consists of X, Y, and Z coordinates,
intensity, color, feature classification, GPS time, and other custom fields
provided by the scanner. LAS files comprise millions of points that accurately
describe the sensed environment or object, making their analysis a challenging
task.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Metaprogram your problems away</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/metaprogram_your_problems_away/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/metaprogram_your_problems_away/</guid><description>&lt;p>Metaprogramming is a useful tool when you want to incorporate general behavior
into your program without having to add extensive boilerplate code throughout
it. This practice is typically employed by individuals who create frameworks or
development tools. The idea behind metaprogramming is to provide you with an
initial insight into how such tasks are accomplished, hopefully inspiring ideas
for future design projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To make sense of all the concepts discussed here, you should be using Python
version 3.6 or later and have a basic understanding of decorators, functions,
and classes. In the case we&amp;rsquo;re studying, we will log the names of functions
called within an existing Python program.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>a golden coin for pleasure</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/a_coin_for_pleasure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/a_coin_for_pleasure/</guid><description>&lt;p>Friday 9:00 AM was the time she would head to my place. I woke up early, did
some cleaning, and started to shower. I had seen her on a website where clients
review the services of the escorts they hire. In her profile, along with
personal details, she had several photos verified by the website and previous
clients. There was a close-up photo of her feet, a picture from behind
emphasizing her ass and feet, a side profile lying naked on her bed with a mask
on, and depending on the ad she was running, a final full-body photo in front
of a mirror showing her face and nude body. The ad&amp;rsquo;s title read, &amp;ldquo;I offer many
additional services that you can take, but everything with protection,&amp;rdquo; with a
&amp;ldquo;NO ANAL, NOTHING NATURAL, DON&amp;rsquo;T INSIST&amp;rdquo; in uppercase at the end.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>File Transfer Between Cloud Services (AWS to Azure)</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/multi_cloud_transfer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/multi_cloud_transfer/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sometimes is a requirement to transfer files from one cloud service to another.
At least that was the challenge that I encountered while developing a file
classification web service. Mid development cycle management changed cloud
provider because of some juicy Azure discounts and the all so great office 365
integration that everyone loves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because of this, the compromise reached to be able to continue at the same
development speed and still lower the cloud services bill, was to continue to
work on AWS in the web service, but the files, after finished the process, must
be transferred to Azure.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the gods are watching</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_gods_are_watching/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:43:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_gods_are_watching/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was standing outside the building where she lived, it was 7 p.m. That was
the time we had agreed to meet that Friday. We had been neighbors for several
months. Although from my room&amp;rsquo;s window, I could only see one corner of her
building, and her balcony faced the opposite direction of mine, I always had
the romantic dream of exchanging glances from our apartments. In the end, it
didn&amp;rsquo;t matter, the mere possibility of seeing each other more often naturally
and spontaneously justified all the romantic scenarios of reunion in complex
and unlikely moments of everyday life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>my number 1 admirer</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/my_number_1_admirer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:42:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/my_number_1_admirer/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the morning, two Facebook notifications, one text message, and a friend
request came to my phone. &amp;ldquo;I really liked your stories,&amp;rdquo; said the message, both
the message and the friend request came from the same person. Curious, I
accepted and checked their photos, hoping it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a fake profile. To my
surprise, it was a beautiful woman with alluring swimsuit pictures, but that
had nothing to do with my exhaustive review.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>guardians of desire</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/guardians_of_desire/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:42:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/guardians_of_desire/</guid><description>&lt;p>She was sitting in front of me, staring at her tea. Her body was present, but
her mind was elsewhere, a place I couldn&amp;rsquo;t reach. To get her attention, I tried
a straw magic trick, only to spill my drink. She laughed briefly, returning
from wherever her mind had been.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;d been interested in her for a while, liking her more than a friend. After
much effort and her hesitant interest in leaving the city, we finally planned a
visit to a small town. There was a cozy bar for beer and a convenient hotel
nearby. The perfect plan: start with coffee, progress to drinks, and spend the
night together. Not our first outing, but the first time I wanted to spend the
night.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the executive bar</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_executive_bar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:42:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_executive_bar/</guid><description>&lt;p>I saw her standing on a corner, and if not for the silent wind gently moving
her hair, she looked like the most beautiful work of art, something to be
admired from afar and not touched.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When I finally walked close enough, the combination of her perfume and natural
scent made my mouth smile against my will. I heard a &amp;ldquo;Hello&amp;rdquo; over my shoulder,
and as I turned my face, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop hoping this wasn&amp;rsquo;t a dream. Even in
the numerous nights I had been alone in my bed, imagining a similar moment,
there was never a woman as beautiful as her.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the best day of my life</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_best_day_of_my_life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:41:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_best_day_of_my_life/</guid><description>&lt;p>There she was, a woman of unparalleled beauty, speaking words I wanted to hear
with a sweet tone, her fixed, flirtatious gaze making me feel just the way I
wanted. The combination of these traits and her gentle facial expressions make
life&amp;rsquo;s optimistic proposals feel achievable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Her name is Daniela. She invited my close friend, Andrés, and me to spend the
night on a mountain near the town. We would sit around a bonfire with her and
two of her friends. As I listened, a mental image of that promising night
formed. I could feel the warmth of the fire, hear laughter in endless
conversations, and my sight dazzled by fire, moon, and flashes of immortalizing
cameras.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Endava</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/endava/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/endava/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="math-engine">Math Engine&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Helped develop a math engine for Quote Sizing and Investment Analysis in Real
State Loans. My main contributions for the project where:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Creating automatic test generation through the use of test JSON files that
contained the different testing scenarios.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Multi-objective or optimization space binary search to find the maximum loan
amount and the minimum net operating income for a desired loan amount.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Open Source version of the package in &lt;a href="https://github.com/jacobitosuperstar/go-cre-loan-calculations">Go&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LaunchMobility</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/launchmobility/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/launchmobility/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="launchmobility-backend-platform">LaunchMobility Backend Platform&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Had no achievements and couldn&amp;rsquo;t do anything notable within the platform of the
company. Culture shock with the company. My way of work wasn&amp;rsquo;t a match and I
felt that changing my way of doing things to fulfill the company&amp;rsquo;s needs
required a great effort that was only useful in that place and time, but not
for my overall development as a programmer. Bummer, but that happens. Sometimes
you don&amp;rsquo;t mesh with the team.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sophos Solutions</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/sophos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/sophos/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="monitoring-platform-for-mines">Monitoring Platform for Mines&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Continue the development and scalling of a mine monitoring platform to mitigate
geological risk.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because there was a communication gap between the Spanish speaking team, that
started the platform and the English speaking team that was going to continue
developing it, my role at the beginning was to be a communication bridge
between the Spanish talking team members and the English speaking team members
on a technical level, and thanks to that, we were able to understand and
document the base code, fix the infrastructure problems that we were having
with Kubernetes and deliver the needed results to the client.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ActiveOne</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/activeone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/activeone/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="proceedings-digitalizationclassificationstorage-platform">Proceedings Digitalization/Classification/Storage Platform&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Helped develop and maintain code from a web application, on which we could
upload scanned proceedings to classify them using different AI services from
AWS.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Two of my notable developments were:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Creating a tool to transfer files between the AWS and Azure storage services
through a stream of data from one service to another.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Creating a base Metaclass and a function decorator to log all the
functionality of the application without having to add anything else than to
add the Metaclass to the class and just a decorator to the different functions
that were critical for the platform.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LUJACOL SAS</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/lujacol/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/lujacol/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="company-internal-tools">Company Internal Tools&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Create a web portal for my clients to create orders, keep track of the shipping
status and download required documents for merchandise nationalization. This a
long with automatic emails for reminders and important notes about the
merchandise helps me keep the head count short on the company, prepare the
container in less than a week, and to work as lean as possible, minimizing
expenses.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Institución Universitaria ITM</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/itm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/itm/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="university-indicators-and-academic-monitoring-platform">University Indicators and Academic Monitoring Platform&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Miscellaneous work regarding student retention in the institution was done, on
which two of my more notable developments where&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Create a web portal that monitors all the students who are beneficiaries of
the scholarships awarded by the Medellín mayor&amp;rsquo;s office, in order to generate
early alarms indicating low academic performance and possible desertion, for
the intervention of the university welfare department.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Create an indicator that measures the impact of the university in a student,
measuring if the university turned a bad student into a good one, a good
student into an excellent one, and what happens with the already excellent
students that the university has.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>