<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>STORIES on jacobitosuperstar</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/</link><description>Recent content in STORIES on jacobitosuperstar</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>death of a father</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/death_of_a_father/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/death_of_a_father/</guid><description>&lt;p>My mother and I were waiting for clearance from the hospital to go in to visit
him, my father. At the time of our arrival, he was celebrating his funeral
ritual with a former priest friend of his. His personal nurse was outside
standing with us. We invited her to a coffee. None of us said a word about
anything.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We got there because the night before, his best friend Gustavo, had called us
to tell us about his state, and how my father had been sending his goodbyes
through his cellphone to everyone, except him, my mother and me. I bought the
tickets to Bogota, and we parted the next day at 7:00 am to be at the hospital
at 9:00 am. That was the time when the visits start. His personal nurse got a
call from the priest, we all got up and she went to the reception to talk to
the ladies in charge of the clearance permits. I was the one going up next.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>a golden coin for pleasure</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/a_coin_for_pleasure/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/a_coin_for_pleasure/</guid><description>&lt;p>Friday 9:00 AM was the time she would head to my place. I woke up early, did
some cleaning, and started to shower. I had seen her on a website where clients
review the services of the escorts they hire. In her profile, along with
personal details, she had several photos verified by the website and previous
clients. There was a close-up photo of her feet, a picture from behind
emphasizing her ass and feet, a side profile lying naked on her bed with a mask
on, and depending on the ad she was running, a final full-body photo in front
of a mirror showing her face and nude body. The ad&amp;rsquo;s title read, &amp;ldquo;I offer many
additional services that you can take, but everything with protection,&amp;rdquo; with a
&amp;ldquo;NO ANAL, NOTHING NATURAL, DON&amp;rsquo;T INSIST&amp;rdquo; in uppercase at the end.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the gods are watching</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_gods_are_watching/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:43:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_gods_are_watching/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was standing outside the building where she lived, it was 7 p.m. That was
the time we had agreed to meet that Friday. We had been neighbors for several
months. Although from my room&amp;rsquo;s window, I could only see one corner of her
building, and her balcony faced the opposite direction of mine, I always had
the romantic dream of exchanging glances from our apartments. In the end, it
didn&amp;rsquo;t matter, the mere possibility of seeing each other more often naturally
and spontaneously justified all the romantic scenarios of reunion in complex
and unlikely moments of everyday life.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>my number 1 admirer</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/my_number_1_admirer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:42:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/my_number_1_admirer/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the morning, two Facebook notifications, one text message, and a friend
request came to my phone. &amp;ldquo;I really liked your stories,&amp;rdquo; said the message, both
the message and the friend request came from the same person. Curious, I
accepted and checked their photos, hoping it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a fake profile. To my
surprise, it was a beautiful woman with alluring swimsuit pictures, but that
had nothing to do with my exhaustive review.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>guardians of desire</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/guardians_of_desire/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:42:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/guardians_of_desire/</guid><description>&lt;p>She was sitting in front of me, staring at her tea. Her body was present, but
her mind was elsewhere, a place I couldn&amp;rsquo;t reach. To get her attention, I tried
a straw magic trick, only to spill my drink. She laughed briefly, returning
from wherever her mind had been.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;d been interested in her for a while, liking her more than a friend. After
much effort and her hesitant interest in leaving the city, we finally planned a
visit to a small town. There was a cozy bar for beer and a convenient hotel
nearby. The perfect plan: start with coffee, progress to drinks, and spend the
night together. Not our first outing, but the first time I wanted to spend the
night.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the executive bar</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_executive_bar/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:42:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_executive_bar/</guid><description>&lt;p>I saw her standing on a corner, and if not for the silent wind gently moving
her hair, she looked like the most beautiful work of art, something to be
admired from afar and not touched.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When I finally walked close enough, the combination of her perfume and natural
scent made my mouth smile against my will. I heard a &amp;ldquo;Hello&amp;rdquo; over my shoulder,
and as I turned my face, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop hoping this wasn&amp;rsquo;t a dream. Even in
the numerous nights I had been alone in my bed, imagining a similar moment,
there was never a woman as beautiful as her.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>the best day of my life</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_best_day_of_my_life/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 19:41:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/stories/the_best_day_of_my_life/</guid><description>&lt;p>There she was, a woman of unparalleled beauty, speaking words I wanted to hear
with a sweet tone, her fixed, flirtatious gaze making me feel just the way I
wanted. The combination of these traits and her gentle facial expressions make
life&amp;rsquo;s optimistic proposals feel achievable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Her name is Daniela. She invited my close friend, Andrés, and me to spend the
night on a mountain near the town. We would sit around a bonfire with her and
two of her friends. As I listened, a mental image of that promising night
formed. I could feel the warmth of the fire, hear laughter in endless
conversations, and my sight dazzled by fire, moon, and flashes of immortalizing
cameras.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>