<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>POSTS on jacobitosuperstar</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/</link><description>Recent content in POSTS on jacobitosuperstar</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Python Parallelism for Point Cloud Processing</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/parallel_pointcloud_processing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/parallel_pointcloud_processing/</guid><description>&lt;p>LAS and its compressed counterpart LAZ are popular file formats for storing
Point Cloud information, typically generated by LiDAR technology. LiDAR, or
Light Detection and Ranging, is a remote sensing technology used to measure
distances and create highly accurate 3D maps of objects and landscapes. The
Point Cloud information stored mainly consists of X, Y, and Z coordinates,
intensity, color, feature classification, GPS time, and other custom fields
provided by the scanner. LAS files comprise millions of points that accurately
describe the sensed environment or object, making their analysis a challenging
task.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Metaprogram your problems away</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/metaprogram_your_problems_away/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/metaprogram_your_problems_away/</guid><description>&lt;p>Metaprogramming is a useful tool when you want to incorporate general behavior
into your program without having to add extensive boilerplate code throughout
it. This practice is typically employed by individuals who create frameworks or
development tools. The idea behind metaprogramming is to provide you with an
initial insight into how such tasks are accomplished, hopefully inspiring ideas
for future design projects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To make sense of all the concepts discussed here, you should be using Python
version 3.6 or later and have a basic understanding of decorators, functions,
and classes. In the case we&amp;rsquo;re studying, we will log the names of functions
called within an existing Python program.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>File Transfer Between Cloud Services (AWS to Azure)</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/multi_cloud_transfer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/posts/multi_cloud_transfer/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sometimes is a requirement to transfer files from one cloud service to another.
At least that was the challenge that I encountered while developing a file
classification web service. Mid development cycle management changed cloud
provider because of some juicy Azure discounts and the all so great office 365
integration that everyone loves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because of this, the compromise reached to be able to continue at the same
development speed and still lower the cloud services bill, was to continue to
work on AWS in the web service, but the files, after finished the process, must
be transferred to Azure.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>