<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CV on jacobitosuperstar</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/</link><description>Recent content in CV on jacobitosuperstar</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Endava</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/endava/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/endava/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="math-engine">Math Engine&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Helped develop a math engine for Quote Sizing and Investment Analysis in Real
State Loans. My main contributions for the project where:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Creating automatic test generation through the use of test JSON files that
contained the different testing scenarios.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Multi-objective or optimization space binary search to find the maximum loan
amount and the minimum net operating income for a desired loan amount.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Open Source version of the package in &lt;a href="https://github.com/jacobitosuperstar/go-cre-loan-calculations">Go&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LaunchMobility</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/launchmobility/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/launchmobility/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="launchmobility-backend-platform">LaunchMobility Backend Platform&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Had no achievements and couldn&amp;rsquo;t do anything notable within the platform of the
company. Culture shock with the company. My way of work wasn&amp;rsquo;t a match and I
felt that changing my way of doing things to fulfill the company&amp;rsquo;s needs
required a great effort that was only useful in that place and time, but not
for my overall development as a programmer. Bummer, but that happens. Sometimes
you don&amp;rsquo;t mesh with the team.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sophos Solutions</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/sophos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/sophos/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="monitoring-platform-for-mines">Monitoring Platform for Mines&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Continue the development and scalling of a mine monitoring platform to mitigate
geological risk.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because there was a communication gap between the Spanish speaking team, that
started the platform and the English speaking team that was going to continue
developing it, my role at the beginning was to be a communication bridge
between the Spanish talking team members and the English speaking team members
on a technical level, and thanks to that, we were able to understand and
document the base code, fix the infrastructure problems that we were having
with Kubernetes and deliver the needed results to the client.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ActiveOne</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/activeone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/activeone/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="proceedings-digitalizationclassificationstorage-platform">Proceedings Digitalization/Classification/Storage Platform&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Helped develop and maintain code from a web application, on which we could
upload scanned proceedings to classify them using different AI services from
AWS.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Two of my notable developments were:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Creating a tool to transfer files between the AWS and Azure storage services
through a stream of data from one service to another.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Creating a base Metaclass and a function decorator to log all the
functionality of the application without having to add anything else than to
add the Metaclass to the class and just a decorator to the different functions
that were critical for the platform.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LUJACOL SAS</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/lujacol/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/lujacol/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="company-internal-tools">Company Internal Tools&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Create a web portal for my clients to create orders, keep track of the shipping
status and download required documents for merchandise nationalization. This a
long with automatic emails for reminders and important notes about the
merchandise helps me keep the head count short on the company, prepare the
container in less than a week, and to work as lean as possible, minimizing
expenses.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Institución Universitaria ITM</title><link>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/itm/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>//jacobobedoya.com/en/cv/itm/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="university-indicators-and-academic-monitoring-platform">University Indicators and Academic Monitoring Platform&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Miscellaneous work regarding student retention in the institution was done, on
which two of my more notable developments where&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Create a web portal that monitors all the students who are beneficiaries of
the scholarships awarded by the Medellín mayor&amp;rsquo;s office, in order to generate
early alarms indicating low academic performance and possible desertion, for
the intervention of the university welfare department.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Create an indicator that measures the impact of the university in a student,
measuring if the university turned a bad student into a good one, a good
student into an excellent one, and what happens with the already excellent
students that the university has.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>